princess.com 2003-06-17

# Princess Where I Belong: contact

Princess Cruises is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy and helping you make the most of your time on the Internet within a trusted environment. The Princess Cruises Privacy Policy applies to Princess's website and governs its data collection, usage and services. This privacy policy discloses how we collect, protect, use and share information gathered about you on our website. We hope that this disclosure will help increase your confidence in our website and enhance your experience on the Internet.

**Information We Collect**  
You can use our website without divulging any personally identifiable information including your email address. Our website does not collect personally identifiable information about individuals except when such individuals specifically provide such information on a voluntary basis, such as when registering at our website, requesting a brochure or video, or accessing our cruise booking application. Princess uses such information collected to improve and customize the content you see, to provide the products, services or membership benefits you request, and to contact you about special promotions and new products.

**Use of Cookies**  
Our website uses "cookies" to help personalize your online experience, such as recognizing your name when you revisit. A cookie is a text file that is anonymously placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. We will not share or sell information contained within cookies with any other person or third party.

You also have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of our website or have some of our services, such as planning a cruise, making a reservation, or being automatically recognized as a registered user, function properly.

**Registering at Our Website**  
When you register at our website, we request your email address. To protect your privacy, we also ask that you select a password. We do not sell our subscribers' email addresses to third parties. We may share your email address with third parties to deliver information about cruise promotions, news and other information about our website on Princess' behalf.

**Email Promotions**  
You may subscribe to our email promotions program by registering on our website and ensuring that Personal Choice WebSavers is selected. By using a password when registering, you are securing your subscription to receive email promotions. You may unsubscribe or change your email address for email promotions at any time by following the instructions mentioned prominently within each email promotion.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
We will occasionally amend this privacy policy to reflect company and customer feedback. We encourage you to periodically review this policy to be informed of how Princess is committed to protecting your information and providing you with improved content on our website in order to enhance your online cruise planning experience.

**Your Comments are Appreciated**  
If you have any questions or comments regarding our privacy policy or our website, you can send us an email at [info@princesscruises.com](mailto:info@princesscruises.com).
